[
    {
        "answer": "el",
        "question": "He was known to his supporters as \"the Desired\" (__________ Deseado) and to his detractors as the \"Felon King\" (el Rey Fel\u00f3n).",
        "similar_words": [
            "scenic railway",
            "tube",
            "elevated railway",
            "funicular"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "right",
        "question": "After being overthrown by Napoleon in 1808 he linked his monarchy to counter-revolution and reactionary policies that produced a deep rift in Spain between his forces on the __________ and liberals on the left.",
        "similar_words": [
            "version",
            "swerving",
            "plot",
            "railway yard"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "constitution",
        "question": "He reestablished the absolutist monarchy and rejected the liberal __________ of 1812.",
        "similar_words": [
            "analyticity",
            "icebreaker",
            "blue law",
            "poor law"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "press",
        "question": "He sup__________ed the liberal press 1814\u201333 and jailed many of its editors and writers.",
        "similar_words": [
            "paviour",
            "troop",
            "phonograph",
            "workhorse"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "war",
        "question": "Under his rule, Spain lost nearly all of its American possessions, and the country entered into civil __________ on his death.",
        "similar_words": [
            "gay lib",
            "feminism",
            "candidature",
            "state of war"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "reputation",
        "question": "His __________ among historians is very low.",
        "similar_words": [
            "renown",
            "glorification",
            "respect",
            "fame"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "king",
        "question": "Historian Stanley Payne says:\n\nHe proved in many ways the basest __________ in Spanish history.",
        "similar_words": [
            "owner",
            "Carlovingian",
            "foe",
            "big businessman"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "commonwealth",
        "question": "Cowardly, selfish, grasping, suspicious, and vengeful, [he] seemed almost incapable of any perception of the __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "lunatic fringe",
            "gerontocracy",
            "oligarchy",
            "Arab League"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "security",
        "question": "He thought only in terms of his power and __________ and was unmoved by the enormous sacrifices of Spanish people to retain their independence and preserve his throne.",
        "similar_words": [
            "electric battery",
            "resource",
            "indictment",
            "permit"
        ],
        "title": "Ferdinand VII of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "succession",
        "question": "She came to the throne as an infant, but her __________ was disputed by the Carlists, who refused to recognize a female sovereign, leading to the Carlist Wars.",
        "similar_words": [
            "nuclear reaction",
            "laying claim",
            "line",
            "radiation"
        ],
        "title": "Isabella II of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Isabella_II_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "reign",
        "question": "After a troubled __________, she was deposed in the Glorious Revolution of 1868, and formally abdicated in 1870.",
        "similar_words": [
            "flush",
            "midwinter",
            "overtime",
            "usance"
        ],
        "title": "Isabella II of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Isabella_II_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "king",
        "question": "Her son Alfonso XII became __________ in 1874.",
        "similar_words": [
            "horse",
            "arbitrageur",
            "knave",
            "champ"
        ],
        "title": "Isabella II of Spain",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Isabella_II_of_Spain"
    },
    {
        "answer": "prophet",
        "question": "He is viewed as the final __________ of God in all branches of Islam, except some modern denominations.",
        "similar_words": [
            "water witch",
            "oneiromancer",
            "worshipper",
            "coreligionist"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "belief",
        "question": "Muhammad united Arabia into a single Muslim polity and ensured that his teachings, practices, and the Quran, formed the basis of Islamic religious __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "education",
            "nitty-gritty",
            "wisdom",
            "food"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "uncle",
        "question": "Born approximately 570 CE (Year of the Elephant) in the Arabian city of Mecca, Muhammad was orphaned at an early age; he was raised under the care of his paternal __________ Abu Talib.",
        "similar_words": [
            "benefactress",
            "fairy godmother",
            "presenter",
            "improver"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "surrender",
        "question": "Three years later, in 610, Muhammad started preaching these revelations publicly, proclaiming that \"God is One\", that complete \"__________\" (lit.",
        "similar_words": [
            "hopelessness",
            "dismay",
            "discouragement",
            "default"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "messenger",
        "question": "isl\u0101m) to him is the right course of action (d\u012bn), and that he was a prophet and __________ of God, similar to the other prophets in Islam.",
        "similar_words": [
            "wanderer",
            "raftman",
            "tourer",
            "fellow traveller"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "hostility",
        "question": "Muhammad gained few early followers, and met __________ from some Meccan tribes.",
        "similar_words": [
            "turgor",
            "misology",
            "wholeness",
            "natural state"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "persecution",
        "question": "To escape __________, Muhammad sent some followers to Abyssinia before he and his followers migrated from Mecca to Medina (then known as Yathrib) in the year 622.",
        "similar_words": [
            "child neglect",
            "child abuse",
            "inhuman treatment",
            "cruelty"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "calendar",
        "question": "This event, the Hijra, marks the beginning of the Islamic __________, also known as the Hijri Calendar.",
        "similar_words": [
            "inventory",
            "reference system",
            "posting",
            "stack"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "army",
        "question": "In December 629, after eight years of intermittent conflict with Meccan tribes, Muhammad gathered an __________ of 10,000 Muslim converts and marched on the city of Mecca.",
        "similar_words": [
            "GAO",
            "Census Bureau",
            "Comptroller of the Currency",
            "Advanced Research and Development Activity"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "city",
        "question": "The attack went largely uncontested and Muhammad seized the __________ with little bloodshed.",
        "similar_words": [
            "province",
            "county palatine",
            "reserve",
            "country"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "death",
        "question": "Before his __________, most of the Arabian Peninsula had converted to Islam.",
        "similar_words": [
            "deathblow",
            "omniscience",
            "drop-off",
            "imminentness"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "death",
        "question": "\"Sign [of God]\"), which Muhammad reported receiving until his __________, form the verses of the Quran, regarded by Muslims as the \"Word of God\" and around which the religion is based.",
        "similar_words": [
            "fag end",
            "terminal point",
            "turgor",
            "shedding"
        ],
        "title": "Muhammad",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Muhammad"
    },
    {
        "answer": "independence",
        "question": "Employing nonviolent civil disobedience, Gandhi led India to __________ and inspired movements for civil rights and freedom across the world.",
        "similar_words": [
            "romp",
            "political liberty",
            "play",
            "enfranchisement"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "father",
        "question": "In India, he is also called Bapu (Gujarati: endearment for \"__________\", \"papa\") and Gandhiji.",
        "similar_words": [
            "instigator",
            "chieftain",
            "Very Reverend",
            "head of household"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "Nation",
        "question": "He is unofficially called the Father of the __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "uninitiate",
            "network army",
            "poor",
            "maimed"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "law",
        "question": "Born and raised in a Hindu merchant caste family in coastal Gujarat, western India, and trained in __________ at the Inner Temple, London, Gandhi first employed nonviolent civil disobedience as an expatriate lawyer in South Africa, in the resident Indian community's struggle for civil rights.",
        "similar_words": [
            "DEA",
            "derivative instrument",
            "FLETC",
            "pile"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "return",
        "question": "After his __________ to India in 1915, he set about organising peasants, farmers, and urban labourers to protest against excessive land-tax and discrimination.",
        "similar_words": [
            "negotiable instrument",
            "resistance",
            "power of attorney",
            "letters patent"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "building",
        "question": "Assuming leadership of the Indian National Congress in 1921, Gandhi led nationwide campaigns for easing poverty, expanding women's rights, __________ religious and ethnic amity, ending untouchability, but above all for achieving Swaraj or self-rule.",
        "similar_words": [
            "crowd",
            "wind tunnel",
            "publicizing",
            "sail"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "nonviolence",
        "question": "Gandhi attempted to practice __________ and truth in all situations, and advocated that others do the same.",
        "similar_words": [
            "recusancy",
            "civil disobedience",
            "passive resistance",
            "job action"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "yarn",
        "question": "He lived modestly in a self-sufficient residential community and wore the traditional Indian dhoti and shawl, woven with __________ hand-spun on a charkha.",
        "similar_words": [
            "gossip",
            "lanyard",
            "agal",
            "tie"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "protest",
        "question": "He ate simple vegetarian food, and also undertook long fasts as a means of both self-purification and social __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "gripe",
            "squawk",
            "complaint",
            "contravention"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "nationalism",
        "question": "Gandhi's vision of an independent India based on religious pluralism, however, was challenged in the early 1940s by a new Muslim __________ which was demanding a separate Muslim homeland carved out of India.",
        "similar_words": [
            "allegiance",
            "secularism",
            "credo",
            "phenomenology"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "way",
        "question": "As many displaced Hindus, Muslims, and Sikhs made their __________ to their new lands, religious violence broke out, especially in the Punjab and Bengal.",
        "similar_words": [
            "deification",
            "virginity",
            "split",
            "collision course"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "solace",
        "question": "Eschewing the official celebration of independence in Delhi, Gandhi visited the affected areas, attempting to provide __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "assuagement",
            "ease",
            "mercy",
            "cosiness"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "harmony",
        "question": "In the months following, he undertook several fasts unto death to promote religious __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "quality",
            "Brahms",
            "antiphony",
            "quiet"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "cash",
        "question": "The last of these, undertaken on 12 January 1948 when he was 78, also had the indirect goal of pressuring India to pay out some __________ assets owed to Pakistan.",
        "similar_words": [
            "pittance",
            "Eurocurrency",
            "underpayment",
            "bonus"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "chest",
        "question": "Among them was Nathuram Godse, a Hindu nationalist, who assassinated Gandhi on 30 January 1948 by firing three bullets into his __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "crate",
            "fundament",
            "flat",
            "wall unit"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "holiday",
        "question": "Mahatma Gandhi's birthday, 2 October, is commemorated in India as Gandhi Jayanti, a national __________, and worldwide as the International Day of Nonviolence.",
        "similar_words": [
            "degree day",
            "Allhallows Eve",
            "playtime",
            "Victory Day"
        ],
        "title": "Mahatma Gandhi",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mahatma_Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "answer": "reign",
        "question": "After her __________, Egypt became a province of the recently established Roman Empire.",
        "similar_words": [
            "school",
            "running time",
            "lactation",
            "prehistoric culture"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "origin",
        "question": "Cleopatra was a member of the Ptolemaic dynasty, a Greek family of Macedonian __________ that ruled Egypt after Alexander the Great's death during the Hellenistic period.",
        "similar_words": [
            "creation",
            "optic disk",
            "node",
            "focal point"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "court",
        "question": "The Ptolemies spoke Greek throughout their dynasty, and refused to speak Egyptian, which is the reason that Greek as well as Egyptian languages were used on official __________ documents such as the Rosetta Stone.",
        "similar_words": [
            "cubby",
            "pull-off",
            "nook",
            "local government"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "goddess",
        "question": "By contrast, Cleopatra did learn to speak Egyptian and represented herself as the reincarnation of the Egyptian __________ Isis.",
        "similar_words": [
            "Phrygian deity",
            "Greek deity",
            "Celtic deity",
            "Graeco-Roman deity"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "father",
        "question": "Cleopatra originally ruled jointly with her __________ Ptolemy XII Auletes, and later with her brothers Ptolemy XIII and Ptolemy XIV, whom she married as per Egyptian custom, but eventually she became sole ruler.",
        "similar_words": [
            "female parent",
            "grand dragon",
            "celebrant",
            "Herr"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "throne",
        "question": "As queen, she consummated a liaison with Julius Caesar that solidified her grip on the __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "academicianship",
            "manhood",
            "regency",
            "public office"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "suicide",
        "question": "Antony committed __________ after losing the Battle of Actium to Octavian's forces, and Cleopatra followed suit.",
        "similar_words": [
            "choker",
            "strangler",
            "racial extermination",
            "throttler"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "belief",
        "question": "According to a popular __________, she killed herself by means of an asp bite on August 12, 30 BC.",
        "similar_words": [
            "noumenon",
            "inspiration",
            "marrow",
            "food for thought"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "pharaoh",
        "question": "She was outlived by Caesarion, who was declared __________ by his supporters, but he was soon killed on Octavian's orders.",
        "similar_words": [
            "emeer",
            "grand Turk",
            "Mogul",
            "regent"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "province",
        "question": "Egypt then became the Roman __________ of Aegyptus.",
        "similar_words": [
            "borough",
            "reservation",
            "political sphere",
            "department"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "legacy",
        "question": "Her __________ survives in numerous works of art and many dramatizations of incidents from her life in literature and other media, such as William Shakespeare's tragedy Antony and Cleopatra, George Frideric Handel's opera Giulio Cesare, George Bernard Shaw's play Caesar and Cleopatra, Jules Massenet's opera Cl\u00e9op\u00e2tre, and the films Cleopatra (1934) and Cleopatra (1963).",
        "similar_words": [
            "present",
            "dowry",
            "prize",
            "largesse"
        ],
        "title": "Cleopatra",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cleopatra"
    },
    {
        "answer": "throne",
        "question": "He was born in Pella in 356 BC and succeeded his father Philip II to the __________ at the age of twenty.",
        "similar_words": [
            "admiralty",
            "viceroyship",
            "feudal lordship",
            "residency"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "northeast",
        "question": "He spent most of his ruling years on an unprecedented military campaign through Asia and __________ Africa, and he had created one of the largest empires of the ancient world by the age of thirty, stretching from Greece to northwestern India.",
        "similar_words": [
            "NbW",
            "SEbE",
            "SWbS",
            "west by north"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "history",
        "question": "He was undefeated in battle and is widely considered one of __________'s most successful military commanders.",
        "similar_words": [
            "philosophy",
            "cognitive content",
            "check stub",
            "water under the bridge"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "age",
        "question": "During his youth, Alexander was tutored by Aristotle until the __________ of 16.",
        "similar_words": [
            "fortnight",
            "lifetime",
            "compositeness",
            "study hall"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "project",
        "question": "Alexander was awarded the generalship of Greece and used this authority to launch his father's Panhellenic __________ to lead the Greeks in the conquest of Persia.",
        "similar_words": [
            "duty",
            "washing",
            "service",
            "missionary work"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "series",
        "question": "In 334 BC, he invaded the Achaemenid Empire (Persian Empire) and began a __________ of campaigns that lasted ten years.",
        "similar_words": [
            "quadratic",
            "alliance",
            "lanthanoid",
            "human race"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "series",
        "question": "Following the conquest of Anatolia, Alexander broke the power of Persia in a __________ of decisive battles, most notably the battles of Issus and Gaugamela.",
        "similar_words": [
            "human beings",
            "biotic community",
            "concatenation",
            "news show"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "empire",
        "question": "At that point, his __________ stretched from the Adriatic Sea to the Indus River.",
        "similar_words": [
            "authoritarian regime",
            "FDIC",
            "palace",
            "archduchy"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "demand",
        "question": "He eventually turned back at the __________ of his homesick troops.",
        "similar_words": [
            "declination",
            "amyotonia",
            "stigmatism",
            "dismantlement"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "invasion",
        "question": "Alexander died in Babylon in 323 BC, the city that he planned to establish as his capital, without executing a series of planned campaigns that would have begun with an __________ of Arabia.",
        "similar_words": [
            "foray",
            "radiation",
            "dispersion",
            "maraud"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "death",
        "question": "In the years following his __________, a series of civil wars tore his empire apart, resulting in the establishment of several states ruled by the Diadochi, Alexander's surviving generals and heirs.",
        "similar_words": [
            "state of flux",
            "finis",
            "flawlessness",
            "terminal point"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "diffusion",
        "question": "Alexander's legacy includes the cultural __________ which his conquests engendered, such as Greco-Buddhism.",
        "similar_words": [
            "phase change",
            "complementation",
            "oscillation",
            "rigidifying"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "name",
        "question": "He founded some twenty cities that bore his __________, most notably Alexandria in Egypt.",
        "similar_words": [
            "benefit of clergy",
            "character",
            "celebrity",
            "big deal"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "culture",
        "question": "Alexander's settlement of Greek colonists and the resulting spread of Greek __________ in the east resulted in a new Hellenistic civilization, aspects of which were still evident in the traditions of the Byzantine Empire in the mid-15th century AD and the presence of Greek speakers in central and far eastern Anatolia until the 1920s.",
        "similar_words": [
            "myelinization",
            "noumenon",
            "heart",
            "heart and soul"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "mold",
        "question": "Alexander became legendary as a classical hero in the __________ of Achilles, and he features prominently in the history and mythic traditions of both Greek and non-Greek cultures.",
        "similar_words": [
            "measure",
            "gumbo",
            "kebab",
            "coin bank"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "world",
        "question": "He became the measure against which military leaders compared themselves, and military academies throughout the __________ still teach his tactics.",
        "similar_words": [
            "physical structure",
            "Neandertal",
            "carpet",
            "blackbody"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "history",
        "question": "He is often ranked among the most influential people in human __________.",
        "similar_words": [
            "unconscious process",
            "cognitive content",
            "quadrivium",
            "episteme"
        ],
        "title": "Alexander the Great",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Alexander_the_Great"
    },
    {
        "answer": "side",
        "question": "It is located on the western edge of Manzanillo Island, on the Atlantic __________ of the Panama Canal.",
        "similar_words": [
            "rhumb",
            "family line",
            "inside",
            "wave front"
        ],
        "title": "Crist\u00f3bal, Col\u00f3n",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crist%C3%B3bal,_Col%C3%B3n"
    },
    {
        "answer": "explorer",
        "question": "Crist\u00f3bal Col\u00f3n is the Spanish translation for Christopher Columbus, the Genovese __________ for whom these places were named.",
        "similar_words": [
            "slipper",
            "scourge",
            "applier",
            "party"
        ],
        "title": "Crist\u00f3bal, Col\u00f3n",
        "url": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crist%C3%B3bal,_Col%C3%B3n"
    }
]